<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Red or Black</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="card">card</string>
    <string name="card1">card1</string>
    <string name="card2">card2</string>
    <string name="counter">counter</string>
    <string name="button1">RED</string>
    <string name="button2">BLACK</string>
    <string name="button3">DOUBLE</string>
	<string name="background">background</string>
	<string name="sound">sound</string>
	<string name="cards_left">Cards\nleft</string>
	
	<string name="instructionsheader">INSTRUCTIONS</string>
	<string name="instructionsheader2">Stage 1 - RED or BLACK</string>
	<string name="instructionsheader3">Stage 2 - HIGHER or LOWER</string>
	<string name="instructionsheader4">Stage 3 - IN or OUT</string>
	<string name="instructionsheader5">Extras</string>
	
	<string name="instructions">
	    A 2 player drinking game where one person is the dealer and the other is the drinker.\n
	    The object of the game is complete all 3 stages without messing up, simple stuff.\n 
	    If at any stage you muck up you drink and start from the beginning (A swig of beer will do or take a shot if you\'re game!).\n
	</string>
	<string name="instructions2">
	    Simply guess RED or BLACK, if correct you will move to Stage 2. If not then drink!\n
	</string>
	<string name="instructions3">
	    Guess whether the next card is HIGHER or LOWER than the current card. Ace is the lowest, King is the Highest.\n
		If correct you will move to Stage 3 otherwise you know what to do…\n
	</string>
	<string name="instructions4">
	    The last stage requires you to decide if the next card is inside or outside the current card and the previous card.\n
	    E.g Current - 5, Previous - Jack.\n IN would be 6,7,8,9,10.\n
		OUT would be A,2,3,4,Q,K.\n
	    You are allowed to call a DOUBLE at this point. A DOUBLE occurs when the next card is the same as the current card or the previous card. E.g Current - 5, Previous - Jack, next card out could be a 5 or Jack.\n
	    Calling DOUBLE is a risky play but worth the glory when you pull it off.\n
	    If you fail… drink heaps!, otherwise if you\'re lucky enough to get a DOUBLE the dealer must consume half their vessel!\n
		If you guessed correctly you WIN! otherwise close but no cigar, start again.\n
		If you win you become the dealer and someone else becomes the drinker.\n
	</string>
	<string name="instructions5">
	    The deck automatically reshuffles when all cards have been used so you can continue getting steamed!. \n
	</string>
	
</resources>
